Guide to the Alvin A. Achenbaum Papers, 1948-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings and Speeches, 1948-2011 and undated
  - Lecture Series
    - Part I Section 2: Definition of Marketing, undated (Box WS23)
    - Part I Section 2: Exhibits, 2007 and undated, (3 folders) (Box WS23)
    - Part I Section 2: What is Marketing, 2005, (6 folders) (Box WS23)
    - Part I Section 2: What is Marketing, 2005-2010 and undated, (8 folders) (Box WS24)
    - Part I Section 3: Competition, 2005, (3 folders) (Box WS24)
    - Part I Section 3: Competition, 2005-2007, (8 folders) (Box WS25)
    - Part I Section 3: Competition, 2007-2008, (2 folders) (Box WS26)
    - Part I Section 3: Exhibits, 2007-2008 and undated, (3 folders) (Box WS26)
    - Part I Section 4: Changes, undated (Box WS26)
    - Part I Section 4: Definitions, 2005-2007, (5 folders) (Box WS26)
    - Part I Section 4: History, undated, (2 folders) (Box WS26)
    - Part I Section 4: Marketing Definitions, 2006 (Box WS27)
    - Part I Section 4: Role of Participants in a Transaction, undated (Box WS27)
    - Part I Section 4: What is Marketing, 2008 (Box WS27)
    - Part I Section 5: Exhibits, 2007 (Box WS27)
    - Part I Section 5: History, 2006-2008, (8 folders) (Box WS27)
    - Part II: Exhibits, undated (Box WS27)
    - Part II: Exhibits, undated, (3 folders) (Box WS28)
    - Part II Section 1: Exhibits, 2007 (Box WS28)
    - Part II Section 1: Introduction, 2006 (Box WS28)
    - Part II Section 1: Marketing Complexity, 2007-2009, (5 folders) (Box WS28)
    - Part II Section 2: Marketing Planning, 2007-2009, (4 folders) (Box WS29)
    - Part II Section 3: Exhibits, 2007 (Box WS29)
    - Part II Section 3: Marketing Plan, 2007-2008, (6 folders) (Box WS29)
    - Part II Section 3: Marketing Plan, 2009 (Box WS30)
    - Part II Section 3: Marketing Planning, undated (Box WS30)
    - Part II Section 3: Useful Marketing Concepts, undated (Box WS30)
    - Part II Section 4: Exhibits, undated (Box WS30)
    - Part II Section 4: Legal Strategy, undated (Box WS30)
    - Part II Section 4: Marketing Plan, 2007-2008 and undated, (6 folders) (Box WS30)
    - Part II Section 4: Marketing Program, undated (Box WS31)
    - Part II Section 5: Exhibits, undated (Box WS31)
    - Part II Section 5: Useful Marketing Concepts, 2007-2009, (4 folders) (Box WS31)
    - Part II Section 6: Summary and Conclusions, 2008-2009, (3 folders) (Box WS31)
    - Part III: Introduction, 2009, (2 folders) (Box WS31)
    - Part III Section 1: Introduction, 2008-2009, (3 folders) (Box WS31)
    - Part III Section 1: Marketing Communications, undated (Box WS32)
    - Part III Section 1: Products and Services, 2009 (Box WS32)
    - Part III Section 2: Branding, 2008-2009, (2 folders) (Box WS32)
    - Part III Section 3: Marketing Strategy, 2008 and undated, (2 folders) (Box WS32)
    - Part III Section 4: Price and Pricing, 2008-2009, (3 folders) (Box WS32)
    - Part III Section 5: Distribution, 2008-2009, (3 folders) (Box WS33)
    - Part III Section 6: Marketing Communications, 2008 (Box WS33)
    - Part III Section 7: Marketing Communications; Advertising, undated (Box WS33)
    - Part III Section 8: Marketing Communications; Advertising Productivity, 2008 (Box WS33)
    - Part III Section 9: Advertising Agency, 2009 (Box WS33)
    - Part IV Section 2: Marketing Communications, 2009 and undated, (2 folders) (Box WS33)
    - Part IV Section 3: Advertising Productivity, 2009, (2 folders) (Box WS34)
    - Part IV Section 4: Advertising Agency, 2009, (2 folders) (Box WS34)
    - Part V Section 1: Media Operations, 2009 (Box WS34)
    - Part V Section 2: Creative Product, 2009, (2 folders) (Box WS34)
    - Part V Section 3: Marketing Research, 2009, (2 folders) (Box WS34)
    - Part V Section 4: Agency Evaluation, 2009 and undated, (2 folders) (Box WS34)
    - Part V Section 5: Agency Compensation, 2009, (2 folders) (Box WS34)
    - Part V Section 6: Advertising is Broken, 2007 (Box WS35)
  - Proofs
    - Part I Introduction, undated (Box WS35)
    - Part I Lesson 1, 2011 (Box WS35)
    - Part I Lesson 2, 2011 (Box WS35)
    - Part I Lesson 3, 2011 (Box WS35)
    - Part I Lesson 4, 2011 (Box WS35)
    - Part II Lesson 5, 2011 (Box WS35)
    - Part II Lesson 6, 2011 (Box WS35)
    - Part II Lesson 7, 2011 (Box WS35)
    - Part II Lesson 8, 2011 (Box WS35)
    - Unused materials, 2005 and undated (Box WS35)